{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Solid Surface Countertop Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40203/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40203,"taskName":"Solid Surface Countertops - Install (Concrete, Stainless Steel, etc)","taskDescription":"Install Solid Surface Countertops","xmTaskDescriptor":"Solid Surface Countertop Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4812,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"corian granite marble counter top","textMessagingName":"Inst Solid Counters","rolloverLongDesc":"Often called Corian, which is one popular brand. Comes in many colors \u0026 can have contrasting colors inlaid in the edges. The edges can be custom molded or cut in a wide variety of shapes. The plastic material on the surface runs all the way through the counter. Many consider them to be more higher-end than laminate countertops.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes Corian, Avonite, Hi-Macs, Staron, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Solid Surface Countertops.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Solid Surface Countertop Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":8,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Solid Surface Countertop Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Solid Surface Countertops - Install (Concrete, Stainless Steel, etc)","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Solid Surface Countertop Project","urlName":"Solid-Surface-Stainless-Steel-Countertops-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Solid Surface Countertop Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"corian,granite,marble,counter,top,countertop,onyx,cultured,steel,stainless,block,butcher,countertops,tops,counters","emcCategoryOid":-12016,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":510,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40203/":{"taskOID":40203,"originalTaskOID":40203,"setID":510,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500643,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this countertop project?","shortQuestionText":"Project Description","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200880,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or replace countertop","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200881,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing countertop","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500101,"questionDisplayText":"Part of larger remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this project part of a larger remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Part of larger remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5102,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Countertop","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of solid countertop material do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5893,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Solid surfacing (e.g. Corian)","answerDisplayText":"Solid surfacing (e.g. Corian)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7050,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood (e.g. butcher block)","answerDisplayText":"Wood (e.g. butcher block)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5103,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the features for your solid countertop. (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9455,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Integral Sink","answerDisplayText":"Integral Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3223,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Inset designs","answerDisplayText":"Inset designs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5740,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink cutouts","answerDisplayText":"Sink cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1633,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cooktop cutouts","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500643,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this countertop project?","shortQuestionText":"Project Description","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200880,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or replace countertop","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200881,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing countertop","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200880,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install or replace countertop","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200881,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing countertop","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500101,"questionDisplayText":"Part of larger remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this project part of a larger remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Part of larger remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5102,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Countertop","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of solid countertop material do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5893,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Solid surfacing (e.g. Corian)","answerDisplayText":"Solid surfacing (e.g. Corian)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7050,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood (e.g. butcher block)","answerDisplayText":"Wood (e.g. butcher block)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5893,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Solid surfacing (e.g. Corian)","answerDisplayText":"Solid surfacing (e.g. Corian)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7050,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wood (e.g. butcher block)","answerDisplayText":"Wood (e.g. butcher block)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5103,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the features for your solid countertop. (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9455,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Integral Sink","answerDisplayText":"Integral Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3223,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Inset designs","answerDisplayText":"Inset designs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5740,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink cutouts","answerDisplayText":"Sink cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1633,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cooktop cutouts","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9455,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Integral Sink","answerDisplayText":"Integral Sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3223,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Inset designs","answerDisplayText":"Inset designs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5740,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sink cutouts","answerDisplayText":"Sink cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1633,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cooktop cutouts","answerDisplayText":"Cooktop cutouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}